notable.ca 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Notable Life

* * *

## Notable Life Inc. (“Notablelife.com”) is committed to honoring the privacy of its users.

Our Privacy Policy, describes how Notable.ca uses your personal information (such as name, email address, age, and phone number) and other information, collected through http://www.Notablelife.com.

Your privacy is important to us. Notable.ca is committed to protecting the privacy, confidentiality, security and accuracy of the personal information we collect, use and disclose in accordance with applicable legislation. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) is a statement of principles and guidelines outlining how we collect, use, disclose and protect the information we collect when you use our Web site and/or register for our email.

By submitting personal information to Notablelife.com, you agree that we may collect, use and disclose such personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you may refuse or withdraw your consent to certain of the identified purposes at any time by contacting us. If you refuse or withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide you or continue to provide you with certain services or information that may be of value to you.

Canadian privacy legislation defines personal information broadly as information about “an identifiable individual” or as information that allows an individual to be identified. The types of personal information that we may collect from you from time to time include: your name, telephone number, and e-mail address. In addition, from time to time, we may ask you to provide us with more detailed information regarding your interests, occupation, and background. For example, we sometimes ask our customers to complete surveys in order to get a better sense of who they are and what topics may be of interest to them. Finally, from time to time, we may acquire demographic and other information about you (e.g. your occupation and interests) in order to serve you better. Participating in this type of survey is at the sole discretion of each user.

Other companies also may sponsor promotions, contests and sweepstakes running on Notablelife.com. Notablelife.com web sites that have links on Notablelife.com may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not address the information practices of those Web sites or advertisers.

Although we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system. Unfortunately, no data transfer over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose to us, and you do so at your own risk.
